Guide to the American Association of Family and Consumer Sciences records, 1899-2008.
American Association of Family and Consumer Sciences records,
- Series II. Administration
  - National Headquarters Staff and Operations
    - 2010 Club bylaws, 1973-1976 (Box 45)
    - AHEA staff recognition ceremony, 1978 (Box 45)
    - AHEA annual reports, communications from Headquarters, 1963-1971 (Box 45)
    - AHEA annual reports, communications from Headquarters, 1968-1974 (Box 45)
    - New Views of AHEA Headquarters, 1956-1963 (Box 46)
    - Massachusetts Avenue building sale, 1987 (Box 46)
    - Postage meter, 1949 (Box 46)
    - Hanson, Cobb, O'Brien and Tucker (lawyers) (Box 46)
    - AHEA Procedures Manual, circa 1970; 2 folders (Box 46)
    - Staff binder: codes, lists, bylaws, purchasing information, circa 1970 (Box 46)
    - Personnel Policies and Practices of the AHEA (Box 46)
    - You and Your Career at AHEA (Box 46)
    - AHEA Procedures Manual, 1974 (Box 46)
    - Job Analysis and Salary System Recommendations for the AHEA, 1977 (Box 46)
    - "Building for the Future," slideshow soundtrack, 1968; [reel-to-reel audiotapes] (Box 502)
    - Dedication ceremonies of AHEA new building headquarters, 2010 Massachusetts Avenue NW, [reel-to-reel audiotape, 7.5 inches/second, single track] (Box 502)
    - AHEA headquarters and building dedication, 1989; [VHS videotape] (Box 502)
    - AHEA staffing correspondence, Elizabeth Andrews, Western Union night letter, 1914 (Box 46)
    - AHEA Headquarters newsletter, 1928 (Box 46)
    - Ways and Means, Building Fund Committee, 1948 (Box 46)
    - Management Report and Department Mission Statements, 1979; 3 folders (Box 46)
    - Massachusetts Avenue contracts: releases of Lien, affidavits, guarantees (Box 46)
    - Miscellaneous notes-organization dynamics/effectiveness (Box 46)
    - Board/staff subcommittee on organization (Box 46)
    - AHEA News Briefs, 1977 (Box 46)
    - Tax forms, 1941-1956 (Box 46)
    - Correspondence-finances, library, 1941-1947, 1963-1965 (Box 46)
    - Lillie C. Smith Fund, 1936-1950 (Box 46)
    - Investment correspondence, 1968 (Box 46)
    - Budget, finances, 1932-1936, 1949-1954, 1964, 1971 (Box 46)
    - Balance sheets, financial information, 1990-1993 (Box 46)
    - Financial statements, 1984 (Box 46)
    - Budget information, 1987-1988 (Box 46)
    - Management audit, organizational analysis reports, 1977 (Box 46)
    - Final Report on Management Study for AHEA by Lawrence-Leiter and Co., 1979; 3 folders (Box 46)
    - General Funds Budget, 1985-1986 (Box 46)
    - Headquarters visits-planned, 1979 (Box 46)
    - Headquarters Development committee, 1968-1970 (Box 46)
    - Sensitivity training, 1969 (Box 46)
    - Smithy-Braedon Management Plan, 1985 (Box 46)
    - Flag-official AHEA, 1958 (Box 46)
    - Association seal design, 1924-1936, 1942 (Box 47)
    - Betty Lamp information (Box 47)
    - Betty Lamp stamp (Box 47)
    - Permanent Headquarters gifts and tributes; Anniversary Fund donations (Box 47)
    - 60th Anniversary Fund scrapbook (Box 47)
    - Information Office, 1972-1976 (Box 47)
    - AHEA holiday cards (Box 47)
    - Invitations, 1978, 1982 (Box 47)
    - Staff reorganization and reduction in force, 1980 (Box 47)
    - Reception in honor of Gail House, 1988 (Box 47)
    - Association priorities, 1971 (Box 47)
    - Code of ethics (Box 47)
    - Report of National Office Staff, 1976 (Box 47)
    - Salary scale study, 1945-1947 (Box 47)
    - Grantsmanship Center workshop, 1979 (Box 47)
    - 2010 Club, president's records, 1973-1975 (Box 47)
    - Awards and proclamations for the Association, 3 folders (Box 176)
    - Image of AHEA Headquarters at 20th and Q (Box 26)
    - King Street Court color drawing (Box 26)
    - Print of King Street Court building (Box 26)
    - AHEA job information Hotline-bumper sticker (Box 308)
  - Outside Organizations
    This subseries contains information on the Association's involvement with other organizations, both international and domestic.
    - International Federation for Home Economics
      - 3rd International Congress proceedings, Paris, 1922 (Box 47)
      - 4th International Congress
        - Proceedings, 1927 (Box 47)
        - Reports and correspondence, 1927-1929 (Box 47)
        - Correspondence, 1927-1928 (Box 47)
        - Reports, proceedings, correspondence, 1927 (Box 47)
        - Correspondence and proceedings, 1927 (Box 47)
        - Correspondence, 1927-1928 (Box 21)
      - Fribourg questionnaire, 1928-1929 (Box 21)
      - 5th International Congress, 1934; 2 folders (Box 21)
      - 6th International Congress, 1939; 2 folders (Box 21)
      - 7th International Congress, 1949
        - Correspondence and reports (Box 21)
        - Proceedings (Box 21)
      - 8th International Congress, 1953
        - Correspondence, reports, proceedings (Box 21)
        - Correspondence and reports, 1953-1956 (Box 21)
        - List of Members (Box 21)
      - Correspondence and reports, 1953-1954 (Box 21)
      - Collective membership memos, 1956, 1968-1970 (Box 21)
      - 9th International Congress
        - Proceedings (Box 21)
        - Pre-Congress tours, 1958; 2 folders (Box 21)
        - Plan for formation of United States collective member groups (Box 21)
        - Organizing Committee report, 1958 (Box 21)
        - Preliminary reports (Box 21)
        - Speeches, press releases (Box 21)
        - Correspondence, glossary of home economics terms (Box 21)
        - Counts of Congress participants (Box 21)
        - Official Directory of Congress Participants (Box 21)
        - Banquet Program (Box 21)
        - Official Program (Box 21)
        - Correspondence, publications, planning materials (Box 21)
        - Programs directory, reports (Box 284)
      - 10th International Congress
        - AHEA tours brochure, Family Life Abroad (Box 21)
        - Correspondence, preliminary reports, 2 folders (Box 21)
        - Correspondence and reports, 1960-1963 (Box 21)
        - "Home Economics Education to Meet Changing World Conditions and Needs," U.S. report, 1962 (Box 21)
        - List of Participants (Box 21)
        - Program, 1963-07 (Box 284)
      - 11th International Congress
        - Proceedings and photographs, 1968; 2 folders (Box 14)
        - Correspondence, program (Box 14)
        - Directory, program (Box 284)
      - 12th International Congress
        - Proceedings and programs, 1972 (Box 14)
        - Program (Box 14)
        - List of Participants (Box 14)
      - Members and donations, 1972 (Box 14)
      - 14th International Congress
        - Congress materials, 1980 (Box 14)
        - Correspondence and reports, 1980 (Box 14)
        - Slides and narration, 1980 (Box 14)
      - 15th World Congress, slides, 1984 (Box 14)
      - 15th World Congress materials, 1984 (Box 14)
      - 16th World Congress, 1988
        - Photographs (Box 14)
        - Program and research abstracts (Box 14)
        - Correspondence and reports, 3 folders (Box 14)
      - 18th World Congress-Pre-congress seminar proceedings, 1996 (Box 14)
      - Slides and narration, 1976-1980 (Box 14)
      - Slides and narration, 1980-1983 (Box 14)
      - Slides, 1982-1983 (Box 14)
      - International communications (for 1955 Paris Council meeting), 1954-1955 (Box 14)
      - Permanent Council, 1955-1963 (Box 14)
      - Permanent Council meeting minutes, 1963 (Box 14)
      - Permanent Council meeting minutes, 1965 (Box 14)
      - Permanent Council, 1970 (Box 14)
      - Permanent Council, 1972 (Box 14)
      - Permanent Council, 1974 (Box 14)
      - Council minutes, correspondence, 1976 (Box 14)
      - Permanent Council, 1978 (Box 20)
      - Permanent Council, 1980 (Box 20)
      - Council meeting materials, 1982 (Box 20)
      - Council meeting, 1984 (Box 20)
      - Council meeting, 1986 (Box 20)
      - Minutes, correspondence, reports, 1996 (Box 20)
      - Brochure, 1997 (Box 20)
      - Region of the Americas conference program, 2002 (Box 20)
    - International Scientific Management Conference
      - 4th, Paris, 1929 (Box 20)
      - 5th, Amsterdam, 1932 (Box 20)
      - 6th, London, 1935 (Box 20)
      - 6th, proceedings (Box 20)
      - 6th, Domestic Section papers (Box 20)
      - 7th, Washington D.C., 1938 (Box 20)
      - 7th, Personnel, General Management papers (Box 20)
      - 7th, Home Management papers (Box 20)
      - 7th, proceedings (Box 20)
      - 8th, Stockholm, 1947 (Box 20)
    - Food and Trade: Today and Tomorrow (European-American Symposium on Agricultural Trade); other materials on food and trade, 2 folders (Box 20)
    - International Conference of Social Work, 1928 (Box 20)
    - 2nd International Conference of Social Work, 1932 (Box 20)
    - World Conference on New Education Fellowship (including manuscript presented by Helen W. Atwater), 1932 (Box 20)
    - 5th Biennial Conference-World Federation of Education Associations, 1933 (Box 20)
    - Home Economists' Contributions to International Programs, circa 1960 (Box 20)
    - Foreign associations, 1954-1955 (Box 20)
    - Foreign associations, 1964-1965 (Box 20)
    - Australia, 1937-1939, 1965-1968 (Box 20)
    - Canada (Box 20)
    - Canadian Home Economics Association, 1941, 1958-1959, 1964-1968 (Box 20)
    - Germany (Box 20)
    - Greece (Box 20)
    - India (publications), 4 folders (Box 20)
    - Israel (Box 34)
    - Japan (Box 34)
    - New South Wales (Box 34)
    - New Zealand, correspondence, circa 1960 (Box 34)
    - Philippines (journal), 1963 (Box 34)
    - Thailand, college history (Box 34)
    - United Nations
      - Reports, 1947 (Box 34)
      - United Nations Association, 1959-1966 (Box 34)
      - UNESCO, 1947-1950; 2 folders (Box 34)
      - UNESCO, 1964-1967 (Box 34)
      - UNESCO, 1955 (Box 34)
      - UNESCO, 1981, 1988-1989 (Box 34)
      - Food and Agriculture Organization: correspondence, 1963 (Box 34)
      - Food and Agriculture Organization: reports, Working Party on Home Economics, 1967-1976 (Box 34)
      - World Food Congress [contains photographs], 1963 (Box 34)
    - United States Government
      - Bureau of Human Nutrition and Home Economics
        - Correspondence and reports, 1943-1950; 3 folders (Box 34)
        - Correspondence; home economics research, 1943-1966 (Box 34)
        - Advisory Committee, 1938-1948, 1963 (Box 34)
        - Correspondence and reports, 1942-1944, 1952 (Box 34)
        - Advisory Committee, 1953-1954 (Box 34)
        - Advisory Committee, 1949-1950 (Box 34)
        - Legislative support, 1930-1933 (Box 34)
        - Correspondence and reports, 1926-1950 (Box 34)
        - Reports and hearings, 1926-1950; 2 folders (Box 34)
        - Advisory Committee, 1948-1949 (Box 34)
      - Civil Service Commission, 1967 (Box 34)
      - Defense Advisory Committee on Women in the Services, 1968 (Box 34)
      - Department of Agriculture
        - Rural Area Development, 1964-1965 (Box 34)
        - Correspondence and reports, 1965, 1979 (Box 34)
        - Advisory Committee on Home Economics, 1961-1962 (Box 34)
        - Research, 1987 (Box 34)
      - Department of Labor
        - Correspondence and reports, 1956-1967 (Box 34)
        - Correspondence and reports, 1961-1964 (Box 34)
        - Children's Bureau booklet (Box 34)
      - Department of State-Women's affairs report (Box 34)
      - Federal Trade Commission, 1959-1960 (Box 34)
      - Food and Drug Administration, 1963 (Box 34)
      - Food and Drug Administration testimony, 1967-1969 (Box 34)
      - International Cooperation Administration - Basic Training in Rural Home Economics, 1956-1957 (Box 34)
      - International Cooperation Administration, 1955-1956 (Box 34)
      - Office of Economic Opportunity, 1964-1965 (Box 33)
      - Office of Economic Opportunity, 1967-1971 (Box 33)
      - Office of Education
        - "Enrollment in Home Economics Education and Placement of Graduates", 1952 (Box 33)
        - "Non-degree Home Economics Offerings in Higher Institutions", 1951-1952 (Box 33)
        - Correspondence, 1965 (Box 33)
        - Reports, 1960-1961 (Box 33)
        - Education research, 1950 (Box 33)
        - Home economics in schools, 1957-1966 (Box 33)
        - Correspondence, 1964 (Box 33)
      - Women's Bureau
        - "Women as Workers"; "Handbook of Facts on Women Workers", 1952 (Box 33)
        - Correspondence, circa 1950 (Box 33)
        - Women's Bureau, 1950 (Box 33)
        - Correspondence [contains photographs], 1972-1973 (Box 33)
    - Advocacy Institute (Box 33)
    - American Association for Adult Education, 1946-1951 (Box 33)
    - American Association for International Aging (Box 33)
    - Family Impact Seminar, American Association for Marriage and Family Therapy, 1989-1991 (Box 33)
    - American Association for the Advancement of Science, 1949-1952; 2 folders (Box 33)
    - "Sources of Outside Funds for Home Economics Research," American Association of Land Grant Colleges and State Universities (Box 33)
    - American Association of Schools of Social Work, 1940-1941; 2 folders (Box 33)
    - American Association of University Women, 1959 (Box 33)
    - American Dietetic Association
      - American Dietetic Association Meeting, 1923 (Box 308)
      - Correspondence, 1956-1963 (Box 33)
      - Vocational guidance (Box 33)
      - Committee on Vocational Guidance (Box 33)
    - American Public Welfare Association, 1955-1957 (Box 33)
    - American Society of Association Executives/Greater Washington Society of Association Executives (Box 33)
    - American Vocational Association (AVA) (Box 33)
    - Home Economics Division Policy and Planning Committee, AVA, 1988; 2 folders (Box 33)
    - Association of Administrators of Home Economics, 1993 (Box 33)
    - Association of Administrators of Home Economics/NCAHE/FAHE, 1988 (Box 33)
    - Association of College Professors of Textiles and Clothing, 1971 (Box 33)
    - Home Economics Section of the Association of Land Grant Colleges and Universities, 1921, 1957 (Box 33)
    - Building Alliances to Communicate Food, Nutrition, and Fitness conference, 1993; 2 folders (Box 33)
    - Business and Professional Women's Foundation, 1979 (Box 33)
    - Citizens Federal Committee on Education [contains photographs], 1947-1950 (Box 33)
    - College Teachers of Textiles and Clothing conference programs, correspondence, circa 1950 (Box 33)
    - Eastern Region of College Teachers of Clothing and Textiles, 1950 (Box 33)
    - College Teachers of Clothing and Textiles conferences, 1954-1956; 2 folders (Box 33)
    - Commission on the Status of Women (COSW)
      - Correspondence, 1964-1965 (Box 33)
      - Correspondence, 1960-1971 (Box 33)
      - Committee on the COSW: correspondence, reports, 1961-1965 (Box 33)
      - Committee to Study the Report of the COSW (AHEA), 1963-1964 (Box 33)
      - Reports, publications, 1962-1963 (Box 33)
      - Newspaper clippings, articles (Box 33)
      - Correspondence, circa 1960 (Box 33)
    - Committee of Correspondence, 1961-1964 (Box 33)
    - Cooperative for American Relief Everywhere, Inc., 1961-1962 (Box 33)
    - Coordinating Committee on Collegiate Problems of Teacher Education; AACTE; and Coordinating Council of AHEA, AVA and NEA, 1951-1961 (Box 33)
    - Coordinating Council of the AHEA, AVA and NEA, 1939-1966 (Box 33)
    - Coordinating Council of the AHEA, AVA and NEA, 1953-1954, 1957-1963; 2 folders (Box 145)
    - Council of National Organizations for Children and Youth (Box 145)
    - Council of National Organizations of the Adult Education Association of the United States, 1955-1958 (Box 145)
    - Educational Testing Service, 1957 (Box 145)
    - Family Service America, Pat Langley, circa 1980 (Box 145)
    - French Consumer Purchasing Group, 1952 (Box 145)
    - Future Homemakers of America
      - Correspondence and reports, 1987-1988; 2 folders (Box 145)
      - Organization, 1944-1946 (Box 145)
      - Advisory Board, 1945 (Box 145)
      - Advisory Board, 1960-1961 (Box 145)
      - Correspondence and reports, 1946-1950 (Box 145)
      - High school home economics clubs, 1933-1946; 2 folders (Box 145)
      - AHEA relations, 1965-1974 (Box 145)
      - Cooperative and Competitive Activities-publication, 1960 (Box 138)
      - Publications, 1971 (Box 145)
      - Planning Paper for Consumer and Homemaking Education, 1978 (Box 145)
      - Resource Papers, 1975 (Box 145)
    - General Federation of Women's Clubs, 1961-1966; 2 folders (Box 145)
    - Hall of Fame (of New York University), 1944 (Box 145)
    - Head Start, 1963-1965 (Box 145)
    - Home Economics Commission, 1968 (Box 145)
    - Home Economics Research Subcommittee/Experiment Station Committee on Organization and Policy, 1987-1988 (Box 145)
    - Future Homemakers of America-Toward New Horizons-an octagon shaped poster (Mapcase-folder 3)
    - Chart-Home Economics Career Opportunities-Bachelor or Higher Degree (Box 138)
    - Honorary societies
      - Phi Beta Kappa (Box 145)
      - Alpha Nu (Box 145)
      - Phi Upsilon Omicron (Box 145)
      - Omicron Nu (Box 145)
      - Omicron Nu, 1969 (Box 145)
      - Phi Upsilon Omicron, 1925-1926, 1938-1950 (Box 145)
      - Home Economics Honor Societies officers, 1962 (Box 145)
    - Institute on International Education in Home Economics, 1958 (Box 145)
    - International Food Information Council (Box 145)
    - International Union of Family Organizations, 1964-1967 (Box 145)
    - Iowa State University College of Home Economics Baroda Project, 1960-1970 (Box 145)
    - Johnson Foundation (Box 145)
    - Johnson's Wax, 1961-1964 (Box 145)
    - Joint Council of Food and Agricultural Sciences (Box 145)
    - Kaiser Foundation (Box 145)
    - Manufacturing Chemists' Association, 1964-1966 (Box 145)
    - Mental health, miscellaneous, 1961-1964 (Box 145)
    - National Association of Extension Home Economists, 1962-1964 (Box 145)
    - National Association of Home Builders, circa 1963 (Box 145)
    - National Association of Manufacturers, 1966 (Box 145)
    - National Association of State Universities and Land-Grant Colleges, 1995 (Box 145)
    - National Broadcasting Company, 1945 (Box 145)
    - National Coalition to Prevent Childhood Injury (Box 145)
    - National Committee for the Day Care of Children, Inc., 1962-1963 (Box 145)
    - National Committee on Household Employment, 1965, 1972 (Box 145)
    - National Conference for Cooperation in Health Education, 1945-1952; 2 folders (Box 145)
    - National Conference for Mobilization of Education, 1950-1951 (Box 145)
    - National Conference of Social Work, 1953-1954 (Box 145)
    - National Conference on Citizenship, 1950-1959; 2 folders (Box 148)
    - National Conference on Family Life, 1944-1948; 2 folders (Box 148)
    - National Conference on Health in Colleges, 1947 (Box 148)
    - National Conference on Women in the Defense Decade, 1951 (Box 148)
    - Joint Committee with National Congress of Parents and Teachers, 1931-1937 (Box 148)
    - National Council for Homemaker Services, 1960-1966 (Box 148)
    - National Council of White Collar Workers, 1943-1945 (Box 148)
    - National Council on Agricultural Life and Labor, 1950 (Box 148)
    - National Council of Administrators of Home Economics-Souvenir Publication, Ellen H. Richards-by Andrey Potter, 1968 (Box 308)
    - National Dairy Council, 1965-1966, 1970; 2 folders (Box 148)
    - National Education Association-Home Economics Section, Martha Van Rensselaer, 1916 (Box 148)
    - National Education Association, 1931-1950, 1961-1966; 3 folders (Box 148)
    - Nutrition Education Conference, 1966 (Box 148)
    - National Federation of Business and Professional Women's Clubs, 1964 (Box 148)
    - National Health Council, 1950-1954, 1964-1965; 4 folders (Box 148)
    - National Nursing Organizations, 1938-1941 (Box 148)
    - National Project in Agricultural Communications, 1956-1959 (Box 148)
    - National Research Council (Box 148)
    - National Safety Council, 1942-1945, 1953-1954; 3 folders (Box 148)
    - National Women's Committee for Civil Rights, 1963-1964 (Box 148)
    - Peace Corps, 1966 (Box 148)
    - Presidential Committee for the Employment of the Handicapped, 1963-1966, 1969-1970; 2 folders (Box 148)
    - Conference on the Role of Women in Policy-Making Positions, 1944-1945 (Box 148)
    - Science Research Associates, 1964-1965 (Box 148)
    - Social Legislation Information Service, Inc., 1945-1947 (Box 148)
    - White House Conference on Aging/White House Conference on Families, 1980-1981 (Box 148)
    - White House Conference on Families, 1976-1980; 3 folders (Box 148)
    - White House Conference on Food, Nutrition and Health, 1969
      - Correspondence (Box 148)
      - State chairmen (Box 148)
      - Steering committee (Box 148)
      - Panelists and participants (Box 148)
      - Material we sent out (Box 148)
      - Conference (Box 148)
      - Art bibliography (Box 148)
      - Organizations (Box 148)
    - White House Conference on Food, Nutrition and Health, 1970 (Box 148)
    - White House Conference on Children: program, 1970 (Box 148)
    - Midcentury White House Conference on Children and Youth, 1950; 4 folders (Box 3)
    - Midcentury White House Conference on Children and Youth, 1949-1951 (Box 3)
    - White House Conference on Children and Youth: correspondence, 1958 (Box 3)
    - White House Conference on Children and Youth: correspondence, 1951-1960 (Box 3)
    - White House Conference on Children and Youth, 1960
      - Correspondence and reports, 2 folders (Box 3)
      - Correspondence, 1959-1960 (Box 3)
      - Correspondence and reports (Box 3)
      - Correspondence, Exploratory Committee, 1959-1960 (Box 3)
      - Correspondence and reports, 1959-1960 (Box 3)
      - Correspondence-youth delegates (Box 3)
      - Correspondence-young adult delegates (Box 3)
      - Correspondence-alternates (Box 3)
      - Group discussion reports, AHEA follow-up (Box 3)
      - Correspondence and report (Box 3)
    - White House Conference on Children and Youth, 1970 (Box 3)
    - White House Conference on Youth; Council of National Organizations for Children and Youth, 1971 (Box 3)
    - Wisconsin Coordinating Council of Women in Higher Education, circa 1970 (Box 3)
    - Women in the War on Poverty conference, 1967; 2 folders (Box 3)
    - Women United, 1970-1972 (Box 3)
    - Women's Joint Congressional Committee
      - Correspondence, reports, publications, 1932-1970 (Box 3)
      - Correspondence and reports, 1921-1952; 4 folders (Box 3)
      - Representative to WJCC, 1948-1951 (Box 28)
      - Correspondence and reports, 1954-1960 (Box 28)
    - World's Fair, 1961-1964 (Box 28)
    - Youth Conservation Clearing House, 1951-1952 (Box 28)
    - Youth Conservation Clearing House-Legislative Action documents, 1950 (Box 28)
    - Youth Conservation Clearing House; The Nation and its Children, 1945-1946 (Box 28)
    - Affiliated organizations, 1929, 1949-1951 (Box 28)
    - Affiliations with outside organizations, 1910, 1923, 1936, 1941-1947 (Box 28)
    - Cooperating organizations, 1949 (Box 28)
    - Other organizations, 1930, 1949-1950 (Box 28)
    - Other organizations (Housekeepers' Alliance, Woman's Foundation, etc.), 1943-1965 (Box 28)
  - Program Division
    - Correspondence and reports, 1974 (Box 47)
    - Correspondence, Edna Poyner, 1976-1979 (Box 47)
    - HEIB correspondence, 1964-1973 (Box 47)
    - HEIB correspondence, 1971-1974 (Box 47)
    - HEIB correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box 47)
    - Extension Section, 1969-1973 (Box 47)
    - Family Relations and Child Development Section newsletter, 1974-05 (Box 47)
    - Art Section, 1974 (Box 47)
    - Colleges and Universities Section newsletter, 1981 (Box 47)
    - Colleges and Universities Section minutes, 1970-1972 (Box 47)
    - Colleges and Universities Section-Teachers of Institution Management, 1963-1967 (Box 47)